http://www.powerballnet.com/privacy-policy.html

Powerball Lotteries
United States PowerballAustralia PowerballNew Zealand PowerballSouth Africa Powerball
Lucky Numbers
Gemini Lottery NumbersTaurus Lottery NumbersAries Lottery NumbersPisces Lottery NumbersAquarius Lottery NumbersCapricorn Lottery NumbersSagittarius Lottery NumbersScorpio Lottery NumbersLibra Lottery NumbersVirgo Lottery NumbersLeo Lottery NumbersCancer Lottery Numbers
Lang-EN
English
BUY TICKETS
PowerballPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
PowerBallNet.com Privacy policy
This privacy policy sets out how uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website. PowerBallNet.com fully committed to protecting your privacyIs committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.May change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. Policy last update January 2017Cookie Uses Cookies are small computer files, which are placed onto your hard disc. These are the only way in which we collect information from you. Once you agree to a cookie being placed on your computer, it helps us analyse data for statistical purposes and then to improve the website. Cookies also help tailor your individual likes, dislikes, needs and preferences on a website. Once the information is used, it is removed from our system. In no way do we have any access to information about you or your computer. More info about cookies you could read, What is a HTTP cookie?Cookies are usually automatically accepted, but you can change your settings to refuse them. However, this could prevent you from experiencing the full benefits of the PowerBallNet.com website. More information about Cookies policy Click Here. Links to other websites Our website contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
